



+ 48 535 471 696 skype: gadmaciej



gad.maciej@gmail.com maciejgad.pl



github.com/MaciejGad/ linkedin.com/in/gadmaciej



27/31 Magellana St. Wrocław, Poland

ABOUT ME

I love mobile and I always have my iPhone nearby;) I'm an iOS Programmer with almost 8 years of experience in mobile solutions for business. Since 2011, I created over 20 unique, custom apps both as an individual Developer and as a part of bigger teams. For the last 4 years, I was primarily working remotely with clients from the UK & UAE.

WORK EXPERIENCE

4 years 2015-Present

All in Mobile (AIM sp. z o.o)

Senior iOS Developer

Working on 7 different iOS projects for a highly specialized mobile dev house. Most of the time remotely.

1 year 2014-2015

Ceneo sp. z o.o.

iOS Developer

Developing a mobile app for the biggest price comparison website in CEE with a team of 5 other iOS Programmers.

1,5 years 2013-2014

Droids On Roids Sp. z o.o.

iOS Developer

Working with international clients of dev house and creating 6 mobile apps for iOS.

7 months 2012-2012

Joy Intermedia

Mobile Developer

Creating mobile apps for clients of 360 Degree Marketing Agency.

2 years 2010-2012

Artweb Media

Administrator / web

Developing and optimizing one of the biggest flight booking sites and creating one of the first traveling iOS apps in Poland.

SKILLS

Programming languages:

Swift, Objective-C, Python

Technologies:

REST API, Push Notifications (iOS, Firebase), Data base (CoreData, SQLite, MySql), Location/GPS (CoreLocation, Apple Maps, Google Maps), Version control (GIT), Unit & UI tests, Continuous integration (Travis CI, Jenkins, Bitrise, Circle CI), oAuth2

Libraries:

UIKit, CoreLocation, Firebase, PromiseKit, Google Analytics, Alamofire, SnapKit, Vapor, Kingfisher, CoreData, R.Swift, iOSSnapshotTestCase, SwiftyMocky, RxSwift, AeroGearOAuth2

Tools:

Xcode, AppCode, CocoaPods, Swift package manager, Fastlane, HockeyApp, Crashlytics, Fabric, Answers, JIRA, Jenkins, Photoshop

Languages:

English (Professional Working)
Polish (Native)

EDUCATION

Wroclaw University of Science and Technology

2006-2012

Master of Science - MS, Bioinformatics





+ 48 535 471 696 skype: gadmaciej





github.com/MaciejGad/ linkedin.com/in/gadmaciej



27/31 Magellana St. Wrocław, Poland

PREVIOUS PROJECTS:

Staff Management App

Time	19 months
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Swift, Firebase, Push Notifications, oAuth2, PromiseKit, Unit Tests, UI Tests
Short note about the project	Staff Management app for UK-based company, about 60% of unit test code coverage, extended UI integration tests

Mobile Security Platform

Time	4 months
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Swift, Multi-biometric authentication (voice, face and eyeprint authentication)
Short note about the project	Demo apps for Mobile Security Platform (e.g. authentication using fingerprint, eyeprint, pin code)

E-signing application

Time	2 month
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Objective-C, Swift, MVVM, RxSwift
Short note about the project	Nordic market leader for e-signing





+ 48 535 471 696 skype: gadmaciej





github.com/MaciejGad/ linkedin.com/in/gadmaciej



27/31 Magellana St. Wrocław, Poland

Social media app

Time	3 months
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Swift, RxSWIFT
Short note about the project	A social app that helps users pick the right outfit for any given occasion.

Dance social application

Time	10 months
Role	iOS Architect, Backend developer
Technologies	Swift, Vapor (Server Side Swift)
Short note about the project	Dance social application

Food ordering app for Saudi Arabia

Time	18 months
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Objective-C, Core Data, Core Location, Google Maps
Short note about the project	Food ordering app for Saudi Arabia client





+ 48 535 471 696 skype: gadmaciej





github.com/MaciejGad/ linkedin.com/in/gadmaciej



27/31 Magellana St. Wrocław, Poland

Ceneo

Time	11 month
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Objective-C
Short note about the project	Continuous development of an e-commerce application for the biggest Polish price comparison company.
Link	https://itunes.apple.com/pl/app/ceneo-zakupy-i-promocje/id395672526?l=pl&mt=8

Heureka

Time	2 month
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Objective-C
Short note about the project	Preparation of an app for Heureka price comparison website's Czech market.
Link	https://itunes.apple.com/pl/app/heureka-v%C3%A1%C5%A1-n%C3%A1kupn%C3%AD-r%C3%A1dce/id436106975?l=pl&mt=8

LiveChat

Time	9 months
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Objective-c
Short note about the project	Client application for live chat software.
Link	https://itunes.apple.com/pl/app/livechat/id402466708





+ 48 535 471 696 skype: gadmaciej





github.com/MaciejGad/ linkedin.com/in/gadmaciej



27/31 Magellana St. Wrocław, Poland

OnetDysk

Time	12 months
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Objective-C
Short note about the project	Sharing files application

Soup.io

Time	4 months
Role	iOS Developer
Technologies	Objective-C
Short note about the project	Content creation app that enables users to post images, videos or text to social media feeds.

Fligo

Time	7 months
Role	iOS Developer, Backend developer
Technologies	Objective-c, PHP (backend)
Short note about the project	First Polish flight booking app for iOS